原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
翻譯     停電趕工賽太公  獨醉  油膩希
校對     禮物必須搞怪賽
后期      灰灰是菇涼      時間軸    加森
總監     新浪微博@賽太公
生
活
大
爆
炸
第十二季  第二集
不過我覺得到了蜜月尾聲
But I think, by the end of the honeymoon,
我們真的開始有已婚夫婦感了
we really started to feel like a married couple.
是好的那種  像電視里那樣
But the good kind, like on TV,
-不是像我父母  -是的
- not like my parents. - Yeah.
真正的夫妻是當你可以撒尿不關門
You're not a real married couple until you can pee
而你老婆也無所謂時才算
with the door open and she's okay with it.
我跟你說過我有所謂
I told you, I'm not okay with it.
她愛死了
She loves it.
我們給大家都買了禮物
So, we got everybody gifts.
你們是不是到機場了才想起我們啊
Did you forget about us until you were at the airport?
才不是
No.
我們是到飛機上了才想起你們來
We forgot about you until we were on the plane.
幸好飛機上有無線網
Luckily, there was Wi-Fi,
而我有網絡商城高速送貨服務
and I have Amazon Prime.
我?紐約
I heart New York.
寶寶一定會很喜歡吐在這上面
Aw, the baby's gonna love throwing up on this.
聽我說  這不見得只能代表紐約啊
Look, it doesn't have to just be New York.
這才是其中的奧妙之處
That's the beauty of it.
這個縮寫可以代表很多你們喜愛的事物
Uh, the initials "N.Y." can stand for anything you like.
舉個例子  我聽說有一個
For instance, I understand that there is
知名的老年搖滾歌手尼爾·楊
an elderly rock-and-roll musician named Neil Young.
或許你們喜歡他啊
Perhaps you heart him.
如果對他無感  埃及銀牌乒乓球手
Or if not him, Egyptian table tennis silver medalist
諾哈·亞瑟里
Noha Yossry.
也可以是山口奈奈
Or Nana Yamaguchi,
她是日本的女聲優
the Japanese voice actress
曾給卡通《仙女下凡》配過音
who starred in Sally the Witch.
你上網查了有誰縮寫是N.Y.的嗎
Did you just Google the initials "N.Y."?
飛行時間長而又剛好有網
I had Wi-Fi and a long plane flight.
你推理推理吧
Draw your own conclusions.
兩位  這禮物真是非常有心了  我...
Well, guys, that was very, very thoughtful of you. I...
你們給我買了XXL號的嗎
Did you get me a double XL?
-我跟你說太大了吧  -你說對了  親愛的
- I told you. - You were right, dear.
謝爾頓  感謝函不是這么寫的
Sheldon, that's not how you write a thank you card.
我寫的有哪里不對
What's wrong with it?
"親愛的海倫阿姨
"Dear Aunt Helen,
謝謝您送給我們的這套令人喜愛的餐具
Thank you so much for the lovely place setting.
如果我的字跡看起來不太自然
If my handwriting looks strained,
那是因為這是我被艾米逼著寫的
that is because this is the 16th thank you card
第16張感謝函
Amy has forced me to write.
我忍著用肌肉在抽筋的手腕
The muscles in my wrist are cramping
艱苦地寫完這句子
as I struggle to finish this sentence.
哎喲  哎喲  疼死我了
Ow, ow, oh, the pain.
愛你的謝爾頓敬上"
Love, Sheldon."
行行行
Fine.
"謝爾頓與艾米敬上"
"And Amy."
這份禮物是萊納德與佩妮送的
This one is from Leonard and Penny.
"完美的禮物贈于最完美的夫婦"
"The perfect gift for the perfect couple."
卡先留著  禮物不滿意就把卡甩回他們臉上
Save that card. We may need to throw it back in their faces.
我真好奇會是什么東西
I wonder what it could be.
什么東西都有可能
Oh, could be anything.
一支長笛  一把拆信刀
A flute, a letter opener,
或是帶裸女圖的筆
one of those pens
把筆正著拿  墨水就會變成遮羞的比基尼
where you put the bikini back on the naked lady.
這東西不錯啊
Isn't this nice?
這是什么
What is it?
你懂的  就是...
You know, it's, uh,
就是那個...
it's one of those...
不是  沒作用
Nope, doesn't do that.
或許是糖果
Oh, maybe it's candy.
舔舔看
Lick it.
我才不要舔  你舔吧
I don't want to lick it. You lick it.
我才不要舔  我剛刷完牙
I'm not gonna lick it. I just brushed my teeth.
是你看的弱智科幻電視劇里的東西嗎
Is it from one of your dumb sci-fi shows?
我看的科幻電視劇都不弱智好嗎
Uh, none of the sci-fi shows I watch are dumb.
-謝爾頓少來  -好啦  《西部世界》弱智
- Sheldon... - Okay, Westworld.
但這跟那部劇沒有任何關聯啊
But this has nothing to do with that show,
唯一的關聯大概就是都令人懵逼
other than it's also inexplicable.
萊納德與佩妮是我們最好的朋友
Well, Leonard and Penny are our best friends.
他們比誰都了解我們倆
They know us better than anyone.
他們說這是完美的禮物
They said it's the perfect gift.
那我們肯定是漏了什么細節
We must be missing something.
你不會...
You don't...
覺得這是婚姻"輔助棒"吧
think it's a marital aid, do you?
別犯傻了
Don't be silly.
艾米  這根玻璃大棒哪里能輔助我們的婚姻啊
Amy, how is this big glass shaft going to aid our marriage?
你覺得當超級狗英雄在外面亂飛時
Do you think when Krypto the Superdog is out flying,
超人得拿著撿屎袋跟在它后面嗎
Superman has to fly after him with a little baggie?
這點以前我還真沒想過
Hmm. Haven't really thought about it before.
但超人應該不需要用撿屎袋
But he doesn't need a baggie,
他可以直接用熱能光線把屎給炸了
because he just blasts the poop with his heat vision.
你以前絕對想過這件事
You've thought about it before.
其實我可常想了
Oh, I've thought about it a lot.
斯圖爾特的臉出了什么問題
What is wrong with Stuart's face?
他好像是在微笑
I think he's smiling.
天啊  他們是在聊騷嗎
Oh, my God, are they flirting?
他們早就過了聊騷期
Oh, they're way past flirting.
我抓到他們在謝爾頓的婚禮上親熱了
I caught them making out at Sheldon's wedding.
你確定她不是在幫他做人工呼吸嗎
Are you sure she wasn't trying to breathe life back into him?
應該不是
I don't think so.
當我在心肺復蘇課上伸那么多舌頭時
When I used that much tongue at CPR training,
他們會逼我買下那假人
I had to buy the dummy.
我有課
Ooh, I have class.
我該走了
I should go.
好的
Oh. Okay.
-再見  -再見
- Bye. - Bye.
大家再見
See ya, guys.
-再見  -再見啦
- Bye. - Bye.
她現在是怎么樣
So, what's her deal?
她是真對你有意思  還是想氣自己父母
Is she into you or does she just hate her parents?
我不知道啊
I-I don't know.
我們在婚禮上親熱了一下
We kissed a little at the wedding,
感覺一切很美好
and it was great.
但之后我們沒有好好談過
But we haven't really talked about it since then.
所以我也不知道她對我有何感覺
So I-I don't know how she feels about me.
她摸了摸你的頭
Well, she patted you on the head,
所以我猜她覺得你是個乖狗狗
so I'm guessing she feels like you're such a good boy!
說認真的  你們覺得我該去約她嗎
Seriously, do you think I should ask her out?
必須啊
A-Absolutely.
別讓真愛溜走
Don't let love get away.
愛情是世界上最重要的東西
It is the most important thing in the world.
沒了愛情  生命一片黑暗且毫無意義
Without it, life is dark and meaningless and all you're left with
你剩下的就只有
is the judgmental gaze of your dog
獨自在馬桶上吃完零食后  你家狗鄙視的眼神
as you finish off a bag of Doritos on the toilet.
謝謝你
Thanks.
你真是個好朋友
You're a real good pal.
你現在也是乖狗狗啦
And now you're a good boy!
我無法停止想那個禮物是什么
I can't stop thinking about that present.
我快要發瘋了
It's driving me crazy.
我也是
Me, too!
卡片寫著那是完美的禮物
The card said it was the perfect gift.
但它不是恐龍化石也不是情侶懷表
But it's not a dinosaur fossil or matching pocket watches,
所以我看不出它如何能完美
so I don't see how it can be.
或許是我們想太多了
Maybe we're trying too hard.
它可能很簡單
Maybe it's something simple.
就像他們夫婦一樣頭腦簡單
Like Leonard and Penny.
很好  有道理
Yes, good.
我們只需要進入他們的思維
We just need to think like them.
好
Okay.
有什么禮物能送謝家夫婦
What gift can I get us
來表達對他們進入我們生命的感謝之情
to express how grateful we are to have us in their lives?
你可真會簡化啊
Way to make it simple.
我直接去問他們吧
I'm just gonna ask them.
不行  這會傷了他們的感情
No, you can't; it'll hurt their feelings.
這我無所謂啊
I'm okay with that.
而且他們也會知道你不夠聰明
And they'll know you weren't smart enough
來解出他們送了什么禮物
to figure it out on your own.
你說得對  這真是太討厭了
You're right. Oh, this is awful.
而且我都不能靠撫摸
And I can't even comfort myself by stroking
五角龍脛骨化石來安慰自己
the fossilized tibia of a Pentaceratops.
我們先睡一覺吧
Let's just go to sleep.
一覺醒來我們就能用全新視角來看
We'll look at it in the morning with fresh eyes,
說不定一切就會水到渠成
and maybe it'll come to us.
好吧
Fine.
又或者我們去拆了那盒子  尋找線索
Or we go tear apart that box and look for a clue.
過了我睡眠時間不睡覺去玩解謎游戲
Staying up past my bedtime and solving mysteries?
誰能想到婚姻生活會如此美好
Who knew married life could be this good?
他的臉出了什么問題
What's wrong with his face?
最近很多人都問過這個問題
A lot of people have been asking that.
他在...微笑
He's... smiling.
斯圖爾特  你看起來心情很好啊
Hey, Stuart, you look pretty happy.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
我約德妮絲去約會
I, uh, asked Denise out on a date,
她答應了
and she said yes.
太好了
Aw. That's great.
但別在哈雷面前這樣笑
But don't smile like that in front of Halley.
她最近才開始能一覺睡到天亮
She just started sleeping through the night.
抱歉  我很興奮
Sorry. I'm excited.
我很久沒約過會了
I haven't been on a date in a long time.
我還約會那會兒
Back when I was dating,
我總會穿新內褲  以免"艷福"來了不好看
I'd always wear a new pair of underwear, just in case.
我也很久沒買過新內褲了
It's also been a long time since I bought new underwear.
估計該買了
And I probably should,
從緊身白內褲變成松垮灰破褲了
because these are no longer tighty nor whitey.
老娘要閃人了
Okay, I'm out.
當別人有機會看到你的裸體時
If there's a chance someone's gonna see you naked,
你先修剪梳理好"雜毛"是基本禮儀
it's also polite to make sure you're well-groomed down there.
知道了  霍華德  老娘最近太忙了
I get it, Howard. I've been busy!
你們好呀
Hello.
我想過來親手把感謝信交給你們
I just wanted to pop over and hand-deliver this thank you note
感謝你們送了貼心的新婚禮物
for your very thoughtful wedding gift.
真好  你們喜歡那個禮物嗎
Oh, good. You guys liked it?
喜歡它多過喜歡不是它的事物
Well, we liked it a lot more than things that aren't it,
我就這么說吧
I'll tell you that.
那可太好了
Well, yeah, that's great.
因為我們看到這東西時便想到
Because when we saw it, we thought,
"艾米和謝爾頓必須得有這個"
"Amy and Sheldon just have to have that."
愿聞其詳  把當時的情形描述一下
Oh, do tell. Now, paint a picture for me,
這禮物你們在哪發現的
like where you were when you found it
你們覺得我們會喜歡用它來做什么
and what you thought we'd enjoy doing with it.
你是不是不知道那是什么
Do you not know what it is?
他當然知道了
Of course he knows what it is.
他可是全世界最聰明的人
He's the smartest man in the world.
全世界我可不敢肯定
Well, I don't know about the world.
還有些也挺聰明的中國人呢
Some of those Chinese fellas are pretty clever.
失陪一下
Now, if you'll excuse me,
我要回家使用你們送的禮物
I'm going to return home and use your gift
而且是按它原本的用途來使用
in the manner which it was intended.
他永遠都不會猜到
He-He's never gonna figure it out.
就是啊
I know.
你到底是什么鬼
What are you?!
-我真是要開心壞了  -對啊
- Gosh, this makes me happy. - Yeah.
霍華德  這話我不常說
Howard, I don't often say this,
但你在這真的太好了
but, good, you're here. Now,
你知道萊納德夫婦送了什么新婚禮物給我們嗎
do you know what Leonard and Penny got us for our wedding gift?
-這個嘛  -別回答
- Well... - Don't answer.
我不想知道答案
I don't want to know.
我只想知道你是否知道
I just want to know if you know.
-我知道  -很好
- I do know. - Okay, great.
我認為我和艾米已經猜到了
I believe that Amy and I have figured it out.
禮物是不是尋寶游戲的線索
Is it a clue to a scavenger hunt
它將會指引我們找到真正的禮物
that will lead us to the actual present?
如果你是在問
If you're asking
你和艾米未來幾天是否該滿城跑
if you and Amy should spend the next couple days
尋找下一條線索
running all over town searching for the next clue,
那我只能說  是的
I'm gonna have to say yes.
我就知道
I knew it!
這太好玩了
This is so much fun.
真的好玩死了
Oh, it really is.
萊納德  再次謝謝你
Oh, Leonard, thank you again.
我們愛死那份禮物了
We love the gift.
他知道那是什么了嗎
Does he know what it is?
邊都沒沾上
No, not even close.
他以為禮物是尋寶游戲的線索
He thinks it's a clue to a scavenger hunt.
小爺我開心壞了
So, so happy.
你們送了什么禮物給他們
Well, what is it? What did you give them?
就是我們結婚時
Oh, I-it's just this dumb crystal wand
霍華德夫婦送給我們的一根智障水晶棒
that Howard and Bernadette gave us for our wedding.
佩妮和我想得頭都大了
Penny and I made each other miserable
都沒猜到是什么  于是我們尋思
trying to figure out what it was, and we thought,
"不如把這份樂趣傳給謝爾頓和艾米吧"
"Why not pass that fun along to Sheldon and Amy."
等等  你...
Wait a minute. Did--
你把我送給你們的結婚禮物
did you give them the crystal chakra wand
水晶脈輪能量棒送給他們了嗎
that I gave you for your wedding?
對  我們是這么做了
Yeah, that's exactly what we did.
你說你喜歡這禮物啊
You said you liked it!
對  我是這么說了
Yeah, that's exactly what I said.
尋寶游戲啊
Wow. A scavenger hunt.
真令人興奮
That's exciting.
我昨晚也玩了尋寶游戲
I had a bit of a scavenger hunt myself last night.
我想找遙控器
I was trying to find the remote.
找了一下沙發坐墊底下
I looked under one of the cushions.
沒有
Wasn't there.
然后我把坐墊再掀高一點
Then I lifted the cushion a little higher.
找到了
Bingo.
精彩
Riveting.
你知道這是什么嗎
So, do you know what it is?
我當然知道了
Of course I know what it is.
這是二氧化硅晶體  也就是石英
It's a silicon dioxide crystal, otherwise known as quartz.
你確定嗎
Are you sure?
還我確定嗎  玄武巖是由富含鎂鐵的熔巖
Am I sure? Is basalt a mafic extrusive igneous rock formed
快速冷卻形成的鎂鐵質火成巖嗎
by the rapid cooling of magnesium and iron-rich lava?
我當然確定了
Yeah, I'm sure.
所以是石英
Okay, so it's quartz.
這一定有什么含義
That's got to mean something.
我們對石英有什么認識
What do we know about quartz?
我上網查一下
I'll Google it.
你也可以問我這個
Or you can ask me,
榮獲麥克阿瑟天才獎的地質學家
the geologist who won the MacArthur Genius Grant.
查到了
Got it!
石英一詞來自德語
Quartz, from the German "Quarz"
兩詞發音相同  但英語拼寫多了一個"T"
which sounds the same, but is spelled without a "T".
有意思  沒有"T"
Interesting. No "T".
什么東西非"T"也[音似"茶"]
What is not "T"?
咖啡
Coffee!
我們第一次見面的那家咖啡店
The coffee shop where we first met!
好的  咱們走  抱歉
All right, let's go. Sorry.
難得有人來找我  我不禁腎上腺素飆升
I think I just had an adrenaline rush from having visitors.
拉杰  你能幫我聞個東西嗎
Hey, Raj, will you, um, smell something for me?
看情況
Uh, that depends.
其實不用看  我直接拒絕
Actually, it doesn't depend. Just no.
我在試跟德妮絲約會要用的新古龍水
I'm trying out some new colognes for my date with Denise.
所以你就直接到我跟前
Oh, and you just came over here
炫耀你跟妹子有約會嗎
to rub it in my face that you have a date?
不是
No.
我來找你是因為我需要建議
I came over here because I need advice,
而你是我認識的人里  跟最多妹子約過會的
and you've gone out with more women than anybody I know.
我想你說得對
Huh. I guess you're right.
謝爾頓最聰明  霍華德最幽默
Sheldon's the smart one, Howard's the funny one,
而本公子  很明顯是最花的
and apparently, I'm the ladies' man.
那萊納德呢
Which one's Leonard?
對哦
Oh, yeah, right.
萊納德應該是最沒存在感的
I guess Leonard's the forgettable one.
好  我來聞一下
Okay, let's have a whiff.
聞起來像帕高·拉巴納牌的香水
Hmm. Smells like Paco Rabanne.
你真厲害  我在跳蚤市場買的
Ooh, you're good. I bought it at a swap meet.
名字就叫"聞起來像帕高·拉巴納的香水"
It's actually called "Smells Like Paco Rabanne."
很好  她會喜歡的
It's great. She's gonna love it.
但愿如此
I hope so.
我真的很喜歡德妮絲  我不想搞砸了
I really like Denise, and I don't want to screw this up.
放輕松
Hey, relax.
相信你的直覺  我就是這么做的
Trust your instincts. That's what I do.
這讓你縱橫情場了嗎
And that works for you?
事實上  沒有
Actually... no.
我把自己的人生搞得一團糟
I've made a mess of my life, and I'm...
現在孤苦無依
I'm all alone.
我最好還是假裝要走開接電話吧
Okay, I think it'd be best for both of us
這樣場面不會這么尷尬
if I pretend to get a phone call and just walk away.
行  這樣最好
Yeah, that would be best.
你好  我是斯圖爾特
Hello. This is Stuart.
抱歉  我得接個電話
Sorry. I got to take this.
當然  我樂意做問卷調查
Uh, why, yes, I'd love to take a survey.
這是我們初次相遇的地方
Okay, this is where we first met.
肯定在某個地方有線索
There's got to be a clue here somewhere.
我們坐的是那張桌子
We sat at that table.
你這是做什么
Excuse me.
抱歉  我們在尋寶
I'm sorry. We're on a scavenger hunt.
無視我們就行
Just pretend we're not here.
我找到了
Oh, I found something!
是口香糖
It's gum.
也許他們放在柜臺后面
Maybe they left it behind the counter.
我和妻子在這里相遇  當時坐的就是這張桌子
I met my wife here, and we sat at this very table,
所以如果你好好表現  八年后
so if you play your cards right, in eight years,
你就可以娶這位女士
you could marry this woman.
這是我妹妹
That's my sister.
別說出來  兄妹戀可不好
Well, don't tell people. That's not okay.
謝爾頓  你看  我問咖啡師
Sheldon, look, I asked the barista
是否有人留東西給我們
if anyone left anything for us,
她讓我們在失物招領箱中找
and she said to look in this lost and found box.
但為什么會在失物招領箱里
But why would it be in the lost and found box?
因為我們曾經迷失  結果找到了彼此
Because we were lost, and then we found each other.
這太有道理了
It makes perfect sense.
看這個
Oh. And look at this.
一個吊墜
A locket.
上面的石頭  我打賭是石英
And that stone in front-- I bet it's quartz.
肯定是這個  這個才是真正的禮物
This must be it. This must be the actual gift.
打開  里面有什么
Open it up. What's inside?
沒東西  空的
Nothing. It's empty.
當然了
Of course.
我們共同的生活才剛剛開始
Our life together is just starting,
他們希望我們用共同的回憶填滿它
and they want us to fill it with our memories.
這可能是史上最貼心的結婚禮物了
This might be the best wedding gift ever.
他們還給我們送了副墨鏡
They also left us a pair of sunglasses
因為我們的未來太耀眼了
because our future's so bright!
他們想得太周到了
They thought of everything!
看哈雷的畫
Look what Halley drew.
她在托兒所畫的
Yeah, she made it at daycare.
畫得真不錯啊
It's pretty good, huh?
是嗎
Is it?
非猶太媽媽好嚴格啊
Wow. Gentile moms are tough.
兩位  我要給你們看點東西
Guys, I need to show you something,
但你們得保證不能取笑我
but you have to promise not to make fun of me.
那當然
Of course.
我很擔心約會的事
Yeah. I was worried about the date
所以給頭發染了色  讓自己更加自信
so I got my hair colored to make me feel a little more confident,
結果更顯皮膚蒼白  所以我去做了美黑
but that just made me look paler, so I-I got a spray tan.
你試過沖澡了嗎
Have you tried showering,
看是否能擦洗掉
seeing if you could scrub it off?
試了
I did.
你們需要買新的毛巾
You're gonna need some new towels.
浴室腳墊
And a bathmat.
還有馬桶座圈
And a toilet seat.
一小時后我就得去接她
I'm picking her up in an hour.
我該怎么辦
What am I gonna do?!
你是不是應該說
Don't you mean what are you gonna
"你要嗚巴魯巴怎么辦"
"Oompa Loompa doompety do"?
《查理和巧克力工廠》里的橙色小矮人唱的歌
你說你不會嘲笑我的
You said you weren't gonna make any jokes.
抱歉  我不說了
I'm sorry. I'll stop.
我不會停
I won't stop.
只是噴霧美黑
Look, it's only a spray tan.
幾天就褪色了
It'll fade in a couple days.
你不如取消約會  再安排時間
Why don't you cancel the date and reschedule?
但我超級期待今晚呢
Oh, but I was really looking forward to tonight.
那就去吧  把實情告訴她
You know what? Then go. Tell her what happened.
-也許她會高興  -如果她不高興
- Maybe she'll be flattered. - And if not,
就順路去巧克力工廠  看那里是否招工
swing by the chocolate factory and see if they're hiring.
這不是笑話  這是真心的建議
That wasn't a joke. That was a legitimate suggestion.
喂
Hello?
老爸
Hey, Dad.
拉杰什  真是驚喜  居然在我生日時打給我
Rajesh. What a nice surprise, calling me on my birthday.
對  我就是為這事打來的
Yes. That's why I'm calling.
還有什么生日禮物比得上
And-and what better gift to give you than the gift
我滿足你的期望去娶一個印度女人呢
of marrying an Indian woman, just like you've always wanted.
我的天  拉杰什  這是天大的好消息
My goodness, Rajesh, this is exciting news.
她是誰
Who is she?
你告訴我啊
You tell me.
什么
What?
我希望你幫我安排一樁婚姻
I want you to arrange a marriage for me.
我實在是厭倦了單身
I'm just so tired of being single,
我終于...我準備好成家了
and I'm finally just... I'm-I'm ready to settle down.
我不能隨便打電話給一個姑娘的爸爸
I can't just call up some girl's dad
讓她嫁給你啊
and make her marry you.
現在可不是2015年的世道了
It's-it's not 2015 anymore.
我知道  但我一個人結不了婚  我需要你幫忙
I know that, but I can't do this on my own. I need your help.
那我也需要你的幫助
Well, then, I'm going to need your help, too.
如果我要幫你介紹一個女人
If I'm going to find a woman to set you up with,
你就不能再在網上發你和你的狗
you're going to need to stop Instagramming pictures
穿情侶毛衣的照片
of you and your dog wearing matching sweaters.
行  為了讓你看到我的誠意  我同意
Fine, if that's what it takes to show you that I'm serious.
問一下
Uh, quick question.
你是單指照片分享網  還是所有社交網...
Do you mean just Instagram, or all my social...?
全部的
All of them!
好  說定了
Okay, deal.
好  那我問你一個問題
All right. Let me ask you a question.
你覺得這個女孩怎么樣
What do you think of this woman?
我的天  好漂亮
Oh. Oh, my God, she's beautiful.
這是你要給我介紹的對象嗎
Is that who you're going to set me up with?
不  這是我在泡的妞
No! That's who I'm dating.
但也許她有姐姐
But maybe she has an older sister.
所以我們在里面放了我的照片
So we put a little picture of me
還有謝爾頓的照片
and a little picture of Sheldon in it.
放進吊墜里
In-in the locket?
是的
Yes.
之前是在失物招領箱里的吊墜
That was in a lost and found box?
沒錯
Exactly.
我們把它藏在那里
Where we hid it?
真的  你們送了我們三件超棒的禮物
So really, you gave us three amazing gifts.
你們送了吊墜  精彩冒險
You gave the locket, the adventure
并且讓艾米和我發現只要我倆合作
and the realization that Amy and I can do anything
便無所不能
as long as we work together.
我們給你們寫了張特別的感謝卡
We wrote you a special thank you note.
這些是文字嗎
Are those words?
不是
No.
這是要你倆一起破譯的密碼
It's a secret code that you two get to figure out together.
提示  這是以梵文為基礎的
Hint, it's based on Sanskrit,
但不是你們以為的那種梵文
but not the Sanskrit you're thinking of.
最精彩的在于  你們不能作弊上網查
And best of all, you can't use the Internet to cheat.
因為我們鎖住了你們的無線網
Because we locked you out of your Wi-Fi,
而答案就是新密碼
and the answer to this is your new password.
我不開心了
I'm no longer happy.
各位  好消息
Hey, guys. Great news.
我要結婚了
I'm getting married.
-什么  -不
- What? - No.
我還沒見過她
Well, I-I haven't met her yet,
她叫安努
but her name is Anu.
我父親說她出身良好家庭
My father says she comes from a good family.
30多歲
She's in her 30s.
她做酒店管理工作
She works in hospitality management.
只要我能挺過六到十次約會
So, as long as I can get through six to ten dates
不暴露我的真面目
without revealing my true self...
我就真能結婚了
...this is happening.
我知道我們要送什么結婚禮物了
I know just what we're giving them for a wedding gift.
我的天
Oh, my God.
是的
Yeah.
我希望在約會時展現自己最好的一面
I wanted to look my best for our date,
于是我做了一系列悲催的決定
and I made a series of bad decisions...
其中一個悲催決定被我褲子遮住了
...one of which is hidden by my pants.
你還想和我約會嗎
Do you still want to go out with me?
當然  也許我們可以一起去找尼莫
Absolutely. Hey, maybe we can go find Nemo together.
《海底總動員》中的橙色小丑魚
這個哏不錯
That's a good one.
另外63支蠟筆朋友知道你出來了嗎
Do your 63 other crayon friends know you're out?
你會取笑我一整晚嗎
Are you just gonna make fun of me all night?
-應該吧  -很好
- Probably. - Great.
想吃什么  中國菜嗎
So what are we thinking, Chinese?
好啊  我有點想吃香橙雞
Yeah, I'm in the mood for orange chicken.